https://www.corporatetravelsafety.com/safety-tips/privacy-policy/

Trip Planning
First Time Traveler Tips
-Which Trusted Traveler Program Should You Choose?
Passports – Important Information
-Should I Carry my Passport or Use the Hotel Safe?
-Passport Replacement Tips – FAQs an Emergency Abroad
-Important Passport Security Tips
-Passports – Important Emergency Information
-No Passport? No Problem!
-Create an “Emergency Passport Kit”
Packing Tips
-11 Items Frequent Flyers Pack, And You Should Too!
-Top 9 Carry-On Essentials
-Over the Counter Meds You Should Always Pack
-The Difference Between a Travel Charger and Adapter
-What Every Beach,Goer Needs to Pack, and it’s not Sunscreen
Health & Travel Wellness
Travel Health Is Your Travel Destination Safe?
-Pill Map What is it? and Why You Shouldn’t Travel Without it!
What You Can Do to Prevent DVT In Flight
-Meds You Should Always Pack
-Why you should visit a doctor specialized in travel medicine
-How to Create an Emergency File for Travel
-Are You Prepared for an Emergency Abroad?
MONEY AND ID THEFT
-Six Things Not To Keep In Your Wallet or Purse, Ever!
Cruise Safety
-Cruise Safety Advice You Don’t Want to Think About for Emergencies
Robbery and Street Crime Prevention
-A Street Smart Guide to Avoiding Pickpockets – See Videos –
-Portable Travel Carbon Monoxide Alarm
In-Room Safes- Not so Safe?
-Hotel Room Safes – They May Not Be as Safe as You Think
-How Safe Are Hotel Room Safes?
-Why You Need to Pack a Portable Travel Safe
Flights & Airports
In-Flight
-On Board Theft – Protect Valuables While You Snooze in the Sky
Airport Safety Tips
-Which Trusted Traveler Program Should You Choose?
Top Rideshare Safety Tips -Travel and Home
-Things to Learn From Someone Who Fell Victim to a Pickpocket
Best way to Redeem Travel Miles and Points
Travel Health Is Your Travel Destination Safe?
– US citizens will need to register online before visiting Europe
-USPS Informed Delivery -Sign Up Before ID Thieves Do
-Smart Traveler Enrollment Program (STEP)
-Are You a Data Breach Victim?
First Time Traveler Tips
-Which Trusted Traveler Program Should You Choose?
Passports – Important Information
-Should I Carry my Passport or Use the Hotel Safe?
-Passport Replacement Tips – FAQs an Emergency Abroad
-Important Passport Security Tips
-Passports – Important Emergency Information
-No Passport? No Problem!
-Create an “Emergency Passport Kit”
Packing Tips
-11 Items Frequent Flyers Pack, And You Should Too!
-Top 9 Carry-On Essentials
-Over the Counter Meds You Should Always Pack
-The Difference Between a Travel Charger and Adapter
-What Every Beach,Goer Needs to Pack, and it’s not Sunscreen
Health & Travel Wellness
Travel Health Is Your Travel Destination Safe?
-Pill Map What is it? and Why You Shouldn’t Travel Without it!
What You Can Do to Prevent DVT In Flight
-Meds You Should Always Pack
-Why you should visit a doctor specialized in travel medicine
-How to Create an Emergency File for Travel
-Are You Prepared for an Emergency Abroad?
MONEY AND ID THEFT
-Six Things Not To Keep In Your Wallet or Purse, Ever!
Cruise Safety
-Cruise Safety Advice You Don’t Want to Think About for Emergencies
Robbery and Street Crime Prevention
-A Street Smart Guide to Avoiding Pickpockets – See Videos –
-Portable Travel Carbon Monoxide Alarm
In-Room Safes- Not so Safe?
-Hotel Room Safes – They May Not Be as Safe as You Think
-How Safe Are Hotel Room Safes?
-Why You Need to Pack a Portable Travel Safe
Flights & Airports
In-Flight
-On Board Theft – Protect Valuables While You Snooze in the Sky
Airport Safety Tips
-Which Trusted Traveler Program Should You Choose?
Top Rideshare Safety Tips -Travel and Home
-Things to Learn From Someone Who Fell Victim to a Pickpocket
Best way to Redeem Travel Miles and Points
Travel Health Is Your Travel Destination Safe?
– US citizens will need to register online before visiting Europe
-USPS Informed Delivery -Sign Up Before ID Thieves Do
-Smart Traveler Enrollment Program (STEP)
-Are You a Data Breach Victim?
Privacy and Cookie Policy
We believe it is important for you to know what types of information collected when you visit our site. We do not give out any personal information to any companies. We do not rent, sell, or share in any way any information provided to us by website visitors. Corporate Travel Safety, LLC. (hereinafter “CorporateTravelSafety.com “) values the privacy of our visitors and takes every known precaution to safeguard the information we collect from unauthorized use. The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for “CorporateTravelSafety.com “.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, CorporateTravelSafety.com makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
CorporateTravelSafety.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. “Cookies” that are needed to compile aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our  “Cookies” are pieces of information generated by a Web server and stored in the user’s computer, ready for future access. Each time you access our website; our server finds the relevant cookie on your computer. The information contained within that cookie is then used to customize your experience with our site.
Can I Opt-out of having information collected?
You have the option of disabling your computer’s ability to accept or transmit cookies. This will prevent us from gathering certain non-personally identifiable information from you. You also have the option of removing yourself from any email distribution list that you may have signed up for.
Communications you may receive – Newsletters
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use the email address provided to send you the newsletter. If you wish to no longer receive these emails you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the email communications you receive or contact us directly at info@corporatetravelsafety.com
Our third party service providers
We may use third parties such as an email service provider, to send out emails. When you sign up for our services, we will share your email address only as necessary for such third parties to provide the relevant services.
Legal disclosures and business transfers
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy unless we obtain your consent otherwise, except in the following instances: (i) as required by law, (ii) in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or (iii) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website, (iv) to respond to any other government-related request, (v) to protect our rights and interests (including without limitation, for our own safety), (vi) to protect your interests (including without limitation, for your safety), (vii) to protect the interests of others (including without limitation, for their safety), or (viii) to investigate alleged or actual fraud, misrepresentation or other misconduct.
Data Protection and Security
In compliance with 2016/679 of the European Parliament (General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR), you may contact with concerns at info@corporatetravelsafety.com.
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow industry best practices to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We also comply with the security requirements of 2016/679 of the European Parliament (General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR), that regulates our processing of personal data.
No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to other websites
Our Website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of our Website. If you submit personal information to any of those other websites, your information is governed by their specific privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website that you visit.
Social media features and widgets
Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or us. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature(s). CorporateTravelSafety.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Children’s Information
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. CorporateTravelSafety.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that CorporateTravelSafety.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
Notice of changes to this privacy policy
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our website and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented.
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@CorporateTravelSafety.com.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on Wednesday, May 23rd, 2018.
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
Privacy Policy was last modified:
January 4th, 2020 by Travel Writer
Popular Posts
Can You Fly If Your Driver’s License or ID Card Was Lost or Stolen?
